{
    "id": "c2cc6669319a4e7f9b774f7471d755a0",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We had a press pass but ………………………… refused admittance anyhow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90bdbe52276b4cdc8b770d7c379fa5a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he ………………………. older, his mind regressed further into the past.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to talk about two past events that took place simultaneously. ",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "got",
                "gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "30efb8a7fb924e63b996d3e1bb4de0b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… any regrets over anything I have ever done.",
            "description": "Either don't have or have never had is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "have never",
                "don't have",
                "have never had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1356bb4e8fc249ce8a17992e8aa81086"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made …………………………. the whole story.",
            "description": "Made is followed by a to-infinitive in passive structures.",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeating",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19fb09ee45b3411abae071ae3763e430"
        },
        {
            "question": "Reading books ……………………….. a good hobby.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the ing form reading ing forms are treated as singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cde9c1df7aac4beda357dd6f9e474edd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suma as well as her sisters ……………………….. at the party.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with as well as, the verb agrees with the former.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7e1ec848b294ad8af7f13f7da8facf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "John along with his friends ……………………….. in that house.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with 'along with', the verb agrees with the former.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ea1d366e587420c87f55b1805a53d98"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know where ………………………?",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the verb goes after the subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "does he live",
                "he lives",
                "does he lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab78a433f93f422ead51210ff0782e59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Scarcely …………………………. one project before she started another.",
            "description": "Either had she finished or did she finish is correct here.",
            "answers": [
                "had she finished",
                "did she finish",
                "she finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e305ce63d40406d908ee4e7874819e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘You look tired.’ ‘Yes, I …………………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am running",
                "had been running",
                "am running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "208d40066ca046e089404f8a718e0b15"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each guest ………………………. welcomed with open arms.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4d453389cee411b87b54ba45dc00419"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every student …………………….. handed in their work.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea3ecab1d7774a18b4a09ea7783f2e6d"
        }
    ]
}